[
    
    Smart Home Appliances](https://www.vocolinc.com/collections/smart-home-appliances)[
    
    Smart Lights](https://www.vocolinc.com/collections/smart-lights)[
    
    Indoor Security Camera](https://www.vocolinc.com/collections/security)[
    
    Bluetooth Finder](https://www.vocolinc.com/collections/bluetooth-finder)

Navigation[](https://www.vocolinc.com/search)

Newsletter [](https://www.vocolinc.com/search)[](https://www.vocolinc.com/account/login)[0](https://www.vocolinc.com/cart)

* SHOP

* SUPPORT

   View all results

Cart

Your cart is empty

Add order note Save

1. [Home](https://www.vocolinc.com/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Felion Technologies Company Limited (Collectively “VOCOlinc”, “we”, “us,” or “our”). is committed to doing business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls. Our Privacy Policy applies to all users of [http://www.vocolinc.com](#) (the “Site”). VOCOlinc’s Terms and Conditions (“Terms”) is incorporated herein by reference and is available. All defined terms in the Privacy Policy shall have the same meaning as defined in the Terms. VOCOlinc adheres to the following policies with regards to Your privacy. 

1. ### Definitions 
    
    1. "Non-Personal Information" is information that is in no way personally identifiable and that is obtained automatically through Your simple use of the Site with a web browser or the Service. 
    2. "Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable and obtained in connection with providing a product or service to You. It may include information such as name and address. 
2. ### Information Collected
    
    When You enter the Site, We collect Non-Personal Information such as Your browser type and IP address. Likewise, in order to offer You meaningful products and services and for other reasons, We may collect Personally Identifiable Information about You from the following sources:
    
    * Information You give us on applications or other forms on the Site; or
    * Information You send us via any medium, including, but not limited to email, telephone, and social media interaction; or
    * If You use a mobile device platform to access the Site or communicate with VOCOlinc, information transmitted from Your mobile device; or
    * Information purchased from third parties.
    
    1. Registration 
        
        In order to become a User (as defined in the Terms), You must provide us the following information to create an account: name, email address, address and phone number. VOCOlinc may request other information from You during or after the registration process that VOCOlinc uses to provide better and more customized services to Users. You acknowledge that this information is personal to You, and by creating an account on VOCOlinc, You may allow others, including VOCOlinc, to identify You and to allow VOCOlinc to use Your information in accordance with the Terms.
        
    2. Customer Service
        
        We collect information when You interact with VOCOlinc’s customer service in order to accurately categorize and respond to customer inquiries and investigate breaches of Our terms. 
        
    3.  Using Third Party Services and Visiting Third Party Sites
        
        Information You provide to third-party sites/websites through the Service are not within the control of VOCOlinc and You provide such information at Your own risk. The terms and conditions of use and the privacy policies of those websites that You provide information to through the Service will govern their use of such information. Any information You share with a third-party site through the Service will be collected by VOCOlinc. VOCOlinc will use such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy. 
        
    4. Use of Cookies 
        
        The Site may send a "cookie" to Your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to Your browser from a web server and stored on Your computer's hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off Your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage Your system. Cookies allow us to recognize You as a user when You return to the VOCOlinc website using the same computer and web browser. We use cookies to identify which areas of Our site You have visited, so the next time You visit the site, those pages may be readily accessible. We also may use this information to better personalize the content that You see on the Site. Most browser software can be set to reject Cookies. However, if You reject Our Cookies, certain functionality on the Site may not work correctly or at all. We do not link Non-Personal Information from Cookies to Your Personally Identifiable Information. In the course of optimizing the Site to Our Users, We may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on Your browser. Any information provided to third parties through cookies will not be personally identifiable, but may provide general segment information for the enhancement of Your user experience by providing more relevant advertising. VOCOlinc does not store unencrypted personally identifiable information in the cookies. 
        
    5. Web Beacons 
        
        VOCOlinc also may use web beacons, pixels, anonymous ad network tags, and cookies to collect Non-Personal Information about Your use of the Site and the websites of selected sponsors and advertisers, to collect anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers, and to collect data related to Your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information collected by Web Beacons also allows us to statistically monitor how many people open Our emails and for what purposes these actions are being taken. Our Web Beacons are not used to track Your activity outside of the Site or the websites of Our sponsors. We do not link Non-Personal Information from Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without Your permission. However, because Your web browser requests advertisements and web beacons directly from ad network servers, these networks can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if You had requested a web page from their site. If You are a non-registered Visitor to the Site, the only information We collect will be Non- Personal Information through the use of cookies or web beacons. 
        
    6. Log files, IP Addresses and information about Your computer and mobile device. 
        
        Due to the communications standards on the internet, when You visit the Site We automatically receive the URL of the site from which You came and the site to which You are going when You leave VOCOlinc’ Site. VOCOlinc also receives the internet protocol (“IP”) address of Your computer (or the proxy server You use to access the World Wide Web), Your computer operating system and type of web browser You are using, email patterns, Your mobile device (including Your UDID) and mobile operating system (if You are accessing the Site using a mobile device), as well as the name of Your ISP or Your mobile carrier. VOCOlinc may also receive location data passed to it from third-party services or GPS-enabled devices that You have enabled. Also, as described above in Section 2.C. VOCOlinc receives information when You access third-party web pages through the Service. The link between Your IP address and Your personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties without Your permission. 
        
3. ### Exemptions from Privacy Policy
    
    Our Privacy Policy does not apply to any information You may send to VOCOlinc by email as email is not recognized as a secure communication form. As such, We request that You do not send any information, which You consider private, to us by email. Furthermore, Our Privacy Policy does not apply to any information You post from Our Site to other websites (i.e. Twitter, Facebook, etc.), due to the public nature of such postings. 
    
4. ### Use of Personally Identifiable Information 
    
    VOCOlinc uses and/or intends to use Personal Information to:
    
    * Operate and improve the Site;
        * Provide Users with the Service and other products and services that a User may request or that a User has expressed interest in;
        * Facilitate subscription processing, reviews and analysis;
        * Evaluate User interest and needs in order to improve the Service and make available other offers, products or services;
        * Evaluate the types of offers, products or services We make available to Users and potential Users;
    * Track use of the Services;
    * Provide customer support;
        * Communicate and provide additional information that may be of interest to Users through email or other means, such as special offers, announcements, and marketing materials;
        * Send You reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages, service bulletins, or marketing;
        * Provide advertisements to You through email messages; and
        * Manage Our everyday business needs such as Site administration, management, fulfillment, analytics, fraud prevention, enforcement of Our corporate reporting obligations, Terms of Use or to comply with the law.
5. ### Links/Postings to Other Sites. 
    
    The Site may contain links to other websites. VOCOlinc is not responsible for the actions, practices, or content of such websites linked to or from the Site. You understand that such websites may have their own legal documents to which You must agree to prior to using and that We have no control over these legal documents. As always, You understand that it is Your responsibility to verify Your legal use of a website as well as use of information from the website with the corresponding website owner 
    
6. ### Market Research. 
    
    VOCOlinc may conduct online research surveys in order to gather feedback about the Site and opinions on important issues, through email invitations. When participating in a survey, We may ask You to submit Personally Identifiable Information. This Personally Identifiable Information is used for research purposes, and is not used for sales solicitations. Personally Identifiable Information collected through market research will be used only by VOCOlinc and will not be given or sold to a third party without Your consent or as otherwise permitted by this Privacy Policy. 
    
7. ### Use of Aggregate Data. 
    
    VOCOlinc may combine Non-Personal Information You provide through the Site with information from other users to create aggregate data that may be disclosed to third parties. Aggregate information does not contain any information that could be used to identify You and does not include Your personal contact information. 
    
8. ### When We May Disclose Your Information. 
    
    Except as set forth below or as specifically agreed to by You, VOCOlinc will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information as gathered from You on the Site.
    
    1. We may share Personally Identifiable information in limited fashion to Our contractors and service providers that perform services on Our behalf, including, but not limited to, operation of the Site technology, marketing services, and other related services. Unless You have opted-out (see Section 5.B. below) of such sharing, these contractors also may have access to Your email address to send newsletters or special promotions to You on Our behalf or to send emails to You for purposes such as conducting market research on Our behalf. Access to Your Personally Identifiable Information by such contractors and service providers is limited to the information reasonably necessary for the contractor to perform its limited function for VOCOlinc. We also contractually require that such contractors and service providers: 1) protect the privacy of Your Personally Identifiable Information consistent with this Policy, and 2) not use or disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information for any purpose other than providing us with products and services as required by law. 
    2. If You prefer that We do not share certain information with Our contractors and service provider, as described above, You can direct us not to share that information by contacting us ([support@vocolinc.com](#)). Finally, VOCOlinc may provide content and services to You through websites other than Our own. VOCOlinc will not disclose Your Personally Identifiable Information to these 3rd party websites without Your consent, but You should be aware that any information You disclose on such sites is NOT subject to this Privacy Policy. 
9. ### Security Policy & User ID/Password. 
    
    Our site utilizes various information security measures such as internet firewalls, an intrusion detection system, encrypted data transmission, and operating procedures to protect Your personal data, accounts, passwords, etc. This information is kept completely separate and confidential, unless You have given someone-else Your user ID and password. As such, You should protect Your user ID and password and NOT share it with anyone. If You believe Your user ID and password have been compromised and You have trouble changing your user ID/password on the Site or within the application, please contact Our technical support department ([support@vocolinc.co](#)).
10. ### CAN-SPAM Compliance Notice. 
    
    VOCOlinc and its affiliates fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us. 
    
11. ### Transfer of Ownership. 
    
    If the entire or substantial ownership of the Site were to change, Your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, Your user information would remain subject to the promises of Our then current Privacy Policy. 
    
12. ### Your Acceptance of This Privacy Policy. 
    
    This is Our entire Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. You agree to it every time You use the Site. If We make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, We will notify You by email or by posting a prominent notice on the Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage You to periodically review this page for the latest information on Our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Site or Service constitutes Your agreement to be bound by such changes to this Policy. Your only remedy, if You do not accept the terms of this Policy, is to discontinue use of the Site and Service. 
    
13. ### Questions About This Privacy Policy. 
    
    Should You have a privacy question about the Site, please email Our customer service department ([support@vocolinc.com](#)).

Last Modified: February 1, 2018

SUPPORT

EXPLORE

Newsletter

**GET 10% OFF YOUR FIRST ORDER**

 Your e-mail

PARTNER WITH VOCOLINC

 Country/region United Kingdom (USD $)

Country/region

Australia (USD $) Austria (USD $) Belgium (USD $) Canada (USD $) Croatia (USD $) Cyprus (USD $) Czechia (USD $) Denmark (USD $) Estonia (USD $) Finland (USD $) France (USD $) Germany (USD $) Greece (USD $) Hong Kong SAR (USD $) Hungary (USD $) Ireland (USD $) Italy (USD $) Latvia (USD $) Lithuania (USD $) Luxembourg (USD $) Malta (USD $) Mexico (USD $) Netherlands (USD $) Poland (USD $) Portugal (USD $) Romania (USD $) Slovakia (USD $) Slovenia (USD $) Spain (USD $) Sweden (USD $) United Kingdom (USD $) United States (USD $)

© 2024 VOCOlinc [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

We accept

Visa Mastercard American Express PayPal
